select the "make_reference" tab
now that we have a pixel mapping estimate enter the location here
click the "Run" button
we can see that after one update cycle, the reference image is much improved
now let's update the pixel map again
but we should decrease the filter parameter to (say) 5 pixels
and be sure to update the existing pixel mapping
you can skip to 1:24...
the updated pixel map now looks better
so let's update the reference again
all the settings are good, so just run it
now we can see some minor improvement to the reference image
so let's update the pixel map again, but with a lower filter
you can skip to 2:26...
so let's update the reference image, again...
and update the reference again, with a smaller filter...
you can skip to 3:20...
this process can be repeated until there is no change in the pixel mapping