select the "make_mask" tab
the data input location is good.
the generated mask will be put in the "speckle_tracking" group of the cxi file
click the "Run" button and you should see the progress indicated in the terminal
you might want to skip the video forward to 1:10:00...
clicking on the "view_h5_data_widget" tab, then clicking "update" you can see the location of the generated mask
to manually edit the mask, select the "mask maker" widget in the "Process" menu
adjust the colour scale as needed
blue pixels are masked, clicking on them will toggle the masked state
clicking "next frame" will cycle through the frames in the dataset
in this case I don't see any more bad pixels so we don't need to click "save mask"